Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3 Locals, 2.
  - Local 301
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, June 23, 1937-January 3, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Local 301 General Electric Collective Bargaining and Grievances with Prodedure for Collective Bargaining, October 29, 1937; 9.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Workers Compensation, National Labor Relations Board and Schenectady General Electric with Unfail Labor Practices Charge, January 3, 1938; 10.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, January 4-July 28, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Schenectady General Electric, January 4, 1938; 1.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Pittsfield General Electric, January 17, 1938; 2.
      - Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Pittsfield General Electric and Unemployment, February 21, 1938; 3.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Schenectady General Electric and Company Union, February 21, 1938; 4.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages and Speed-up, February 25, 1938; 5.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Pittsfield General Electric and Factionalism with April 30, 1938, Clarence Mullins Letter to UE and Notes, May 2, 1938; 6.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Pattern Makers Inter-union Rivalry, May 9, 1938; 7.
      - Jandreau to Emspak, May 25, 1938; 8.
      - Jandreau to William Mitchell Regarding Grievances and Wages, July 28, 1938; 9.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, August 9, 1948-September 21, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Unemployent and Workers Progress Administration, August 9, 1938; 1.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, August 25, 1938; 2.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding New York State Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, August 30, 1938; 3.
      - Jandreau to James Matles Regarding League of Women Voters, October 6, 1938; 4.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Detroit Lubricator, February 22, 1939; 5.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding General Electric Conference, March 17, 1939; 6.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Father Coughlin and UE News, March 23, 1939; 7.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers with Graphs and Engineers Statement, April 21, 1939; 8.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Subcontracting, May 11, 1939; 9.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Fedders with May 15, 1939, F.C. Fedders Letter to Jandreau, May 16, 1939; 10.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Wages and Working Conditions, June 8, 1939; 11.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Subcontracting, July 25, 1939; 12.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Quarter Century Club, July 29, 1939; 13.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 15, 1939; 14.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board, September 21, 1939; 15.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, September 27, 1939-October 7, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Leo Jandrau to James Matles Regarding Newspaper, September 27, 1939; 1.
      - Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues, October 2, 1939; 2.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Publication, October 10, 1939; 3.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Grievances, December 15, 1939; 4.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages and Grievances with Jandreau Letter to W. Burrows and Cases Refered to Management, January 10, 1940; 5.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Stromberg and Company Union, January 23, 1940; 6.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Unfair Labor Practices, February 2, 1940; 7.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Unemployment with February 4, 1940, "Factory Employment Rises Throughout U.S. During Year" Works New Clipping, February 5, 1940; 8.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Grievances, February 13, 1940; 9.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Local 301 Picnic, May 7, 1940; 10.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages and Toolmakers, August 19, 1940; 11.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages and Toolmakers with August 19, 1940, G.H. Pfeif Letter to Jandreau and Schenectady Docketon Toolmakers, August 21, 1940; 12.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Conscription, September 25, 1940; 13.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Grievances with September 17, 1940, Jandreau Letter to K.O. Schulte, September 26, 1940; 14.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages and Toolmakers, October 7, 1940; 15.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, December 17, 1940-August 4, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 17, 1940; 1.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages, March 25, 1941; 2.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Local 119 General Electric Contracts, June 2, 1941; 3.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Health and Safety, June 18, 1941; 4.
      - Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Steel Workers Organizing Committee Inter-union Rivalry and American Locomotive with March 31, 1941, Walter Payne Letter to Walter Condee, April 16, 1941, Payne Letter to W.L. Lentz, May 10, 1941, W. Henry Hickcox Letter to Lentz, May 13, 1941, Lentz Letter to Hickcox, July 3, 1941, S.M. Voltiz Letter to Philip Murray and July 3, 1941, Case Sent to National Labor Relations Board, July 8, 1941; 5.
      - Jandreau Letter Regarding Wages and Women, July 24, 1941; 6.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding McCall Refrigerator, July 30, 1941; 7.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Steamfitters Inter-union Rivalry with Petition Copy, July 30, 1941; 8.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Lost Time with Forms, August 4, 1941; 9.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, November 24, 1941-July 10, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Action with November 19, 1941, Irving M. Ives Letter to Jandreau, November 24, 1941; 1.
      - Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Political Action and Smith Act, December 12, 1941; 2.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Productivity, December 20, 1941; 3.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Overtime, December 26, 1941; 4.
      - Jandreau to K. O. Shulte Regarding Military Conversion, January 13, 1942; 5.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages, February 11, 1942; 6.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Conscription with Draft Classifications, April 14, 1942; 7.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Stromberg Carlson and National Labor Relations Board with May 12, 1942, Henry Winters Letter to Jandreau, May 13, 1942; 8.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Stromberg Carlson and National Labor Relations Board with May 16, 1942, Winters Letter to Jandreau, May 18, 1942; 9.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 3, 1942; 10.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Wages and Toolmakers, July 10, 1942; 11.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, October 6, 1942-June 21, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Leo Jandreau to J.W. Burnison Regarding Absenteeism, October 6, 1942; 1.
      - Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Overtime with October 7, 1942, Overtime Payments, October 8, 1942; 2.
      - Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding American-Soviet Friendship Conference, October, 21, 1942; 3.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Absenteeism with October 23, 1942, Burnison Letter to Jandreau, October 24, 1942; 4.
      - Jandreau to Burnison Regarding Black Workers and Overtime, December 4, 1942; 5.
      - Jandreau to Burnison Regarding Holidays, January 5, 1943; 6.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Win the War Conference, January 29, 1943; 7.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding War Production Board, Wages and Productivity with February 2, 1943, C.C. Jessop Letter to All Out War Production Committee and Suggestions, February 6, 1943; 8.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Seniority and General Electric Collective Bargaining, February 9, 1943; 9.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Dues with Report on Membership Status and Cost of Dues Collection, February 23, 1943; 10.
      - Jandreau to James Byrnes Regarding Overtime, April 12, 1943; 11.
      - Jandreau to Henry Rhine Regarding Executive Board Meeting, May 31, 1943; 12.
      - Jandreau to Edward Wallingford Regarding Office Prodecures, May 31, 1943; 13.
      - Jandreau Telegram to Wallingford Regarding Prices and Political Action, June 21, 1943; 14.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, June 30, 1943-May 24, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Leo Jandreau to Samuel Chaukin Regarding Schenectady Draftsmen Association, June 30, 1943; 1.
      - Jandreau to Edward Wallingford Regarding General Electric Athletic Association, June 30, 1943; 2.
      - Jandreau to Harold Garno Regarding War Labor Board and War Manpower Commission, July 2, 1943; 3.
      - Jandreau to Wallingford Regarding Seniority and Grievances with July 30, 1943, Jandreau Letter to W.R. Burrows, August 4, 1943; 4.
      - Jandreau to S.L. Archer Regarding Firings, August 5, 1943; 5.
      - Jandreau to Wallingford Regarding Wages, October 14, 1943; 6.
      - Jandreau to Mrs. L. Vottis Regarding Ladies Auxiliary, November 8, 1943; 7.
      - Jandreau to Sanford Archer Regarding Transfers, December 4, 1943-January 3, 1944; 8-9.
      - Jandreau to Russ Nixon Regarding Firings and Blacklists, January 14, 1944; 10.
      - Jandreau to Wallingford Regarding Conscription, January 21, 1944; 11.
      - Jandreau to Archer Regarding Membership Maintenance, February 7, 1944; 12.
      - Jandreau to Archer Regarding Pensions and Grievances, February 10, 1944; 13.
      - Jandreau to Archer Regarding Wages, February 16, 1944; 14.
      - Jandreau to J. Livingston Regarding Finances, May 15, 1944; 15.
      - Jandreau to Whom It May Concern Regarding Russian War Relief, August 7, 1944; 16.
      - Jandreau to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, Octoer 19-November 16, 1944; 17-18.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, December 27, 1944; 19.
      - Jandreau to Allen Haywood Regarding Factionalism and Congress of Industrial Organization with February 10, 1949, Haywood Letter to Jandreau, January 11, 1949; 20.
      - Jandreau to John Callahan Regarding Local 225, Factionalism and General Electric Conference Board, May 24, 1949; 21.
      - Jandreau to Joseph Dermody Regarding Local 255, Factionalism and General Electric Conference Board, May 24, 1949; 22.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Leo Jandreau Correspondence, December 21, 1950-March 9, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Leo Jandreau to James Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, December 21, 1950; 1.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding International Harvester Strikes, October 13, 1952; 2.
      - Jandreau to Matles Regarding Cheektowaga Westinghouse Inter-union Rivalry, October 22, 1952; 3.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Local 11114 Strikes, September 1, 1953; 4.
      - Jandreau to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 9, 1954; 5.
      - Jandreau Telegram Regarding Buffalo, 6.
      - Jandreau Telegram Regarding Syracuse, 7.
    - Local 301 Incoming Victor Pasche Correspondence, February 11, 1947-May 4, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - William Cahn Regarding Publicity, February 11, 1947; 1.
      - Cahn Regarding Factionalism and General Electric Bridgeport, March 3, 1947; 2.
      - Cahn Telegram Regarding General Electric Contracts, May 6, 1947; 3.
      - Cahn Regarding Publicity, May 19, 1948-March 29, 1949; 4-6.
      - Cahn Regarding UE Steward, April 8, 1949; 7.
      - Cahn Regarding Publicity, May 12, 1949; 8.
      - Cahn Regarding UE News, May 19-26, 1949; 9-10.
      - Cahn Regarding Publicity, August 22, 1949-April 12, 1950; 11-12.
      - Cahn Regarding Meetings with April 13, 1950, Cahn Telegram to S.H. Fasian, April 14, 1950; 13.
      - Cahn Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 24, 1950; 14.
      - Cahn Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 27, 1950; 15.
      - Cahn Regarding Publicity, May 4, 1950; 16.
      - Fred D'Avila Telegram Regarding Meetings, April 27, 1948-March 17, 1950; 17-18.
      - James Matles Regarding Steel Board of Inquiry, September 30, 1949; 19.
      - Matles Regarding Anti-communism, April 17, 1950; 20.
      - Edward Matthews Regarding Time Study, March 3, 1947; 21.
    - Local 301 Incoming Victor Pasche Correspondence, June 22, 1948-February 27, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Nat Spero Regarding Publicity, February 27, 1950; 1.
      - Tom Wright Telegram, June 22, 1948; 2.
      - Wright Telegram Regarding UE News, November 23, 1948; 3.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Victor Pasche Correspondence, February 26, 1947-April 4, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Victor Pasche to William Cahn Regarding Publicity, February 26, 1947; 1.
      - Pasche Edward Matthew Regarding Piece Work, February 26, 1947; 2.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity and Bridgeport General Electric, February 28, 1947; 3.
      - Pasche Telegram to Cahn Regarding General Electric Contracts, May 6, 1947; 4.
      - Pasche to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Publicity, May 23, 1947; 5.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity, May 11, 1948; 6.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity and Inflation with Schenectady Gazette Clipping, May 17, 1948; 7.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity and General Electric Collective Bargaining, May 24, 1948; 8.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity, November 1, 1948-March 25, 1949; 9-10.
      - Pasche to Joseph Dermody Regarding Publicity and Unemployment, March 28, 1949; 11.
      - Pasche to James Matles Regarding Hoover Strikes with "Labor Federation Discusses Charge of Discrimination", March 29, 1949; 12.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Ford Strikes and Publicity, May 25, 1949; 13.
      - Pasche to Fred D'Avils Regarding Hours, Unemployment and Publicity, June 21, 1949; 14.
      - Pasche to Emspak Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, August 4, 1949; 15.
      - Pasche to Matles Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization Inter-union Rivalry, December 23, 1949; 16.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity, August 12, 1949; 17.
      - Pasche to Matles Regarding Local 601 and Union Generator, March 18, 1950; 18.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Publicity and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, April 4, 1950; 19.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Victor Pasche Correspondence, April 11-June 30, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Victor Pasche to Thomas Wright Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, April 11, 1950; 1.
      - Pasche to William Cahn Regarding Meeting Hall, April 11, 1950; 2.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, Publicity, Sunbeam Organization, Chicago and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry with Press Release, April 20, 1950; 3.
      - Pasche to Cahn Regarding Pensions and Publicity, April 28, 1950; 4.
      - Pasche to James Matles Regarding Publicity, June 16, 1950; 5.
      - Pasche to Joseph Dermody Regarding Publicity, June 30, 1950; 6.
    - Local 301 Incoming Emil (Rudy) Radosevich Correspondence, November 22, 1942-May 3, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 22, 1949; 1.
      - Barish Regarding Finances, February 24-August 23, 1950; 2-3.
      - William Cahn Regarding Films, February 4, 1949; 4.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 6-19, 1948; 5-6.
      - Emspak Secretary Regarding Finances, December 20, 1949; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances with April 3, 1950, Janet Scott Letter to Emspak, 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 3, 1950; 9.
      - David Ratner Regarding Supplies, February 8, 1949; 10.
      - Ratner Regarding Finances, July 18, 1949-January 13, 1950; 11-12.
      - Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, April 4, 1950; 13.
      - Ratner Regarding Finances, April 10, 1950; 14.
      - David Scribner Regarding Finances, December 23, 1948; 15.
      - Nathan Spero Regarding Per Capita, February 28, 1949; 16.
    - Local 301 Outgoing Emil (Rudy) Radosevich Correspondence, February 10, 1948-August 22, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 45)
      - Rudy Radosevich to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 10, 1948; 1.
      - Radosevich to David Ratner Regarding Supplies, May 21, 1948; 2.
      - Radosevich to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 23, 1948; 3.
      - Radosevich to David Scribner Regarding Finances, December 21, 1948; 4.
      - Radosevich to Ratner Regarding Supplies, January 17-February 1, 1949; 5-6.
      - Radosevich to Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, November 14, 1949; 7.
      - Radosevich to Barish Regarding Finances, November 15, 1949; 8.
      - Radosevich to Ratner Regarding Finances, January 24-February 6, 1950; 9-11.
      - Radosevich to Ratner Regarding Supplies, February 16, 1950; 12.
      - Radosevich to Barish Regarding Finances, February 27, 1950; 13.
      - Radosevich to Ratner Regarding Supplies, March 8, 1950; 14.
      - Radosevich to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 16, 1950; 15.
      - Radosevich to Ray Klausner Regarding Finances with Rachie Memo to Ratner, April 6, 1950; 16.
      - Radosevich to Barish Regarding Finances, April 7-May 26, 1950; 17-18.
      - Radosevich to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 22, 1950; 19.
    - Local 301 Incoming William Turnbull Correspondence, September 26, 1935-January 23, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 46)
      - James Carey Regarding Schenectady General Electric, January 12, 1937; 1.
      - Carey Regarding Finances with April 2, 1937, Mendel Luvie Letter to Carey and April 7, 1937, Carey Letter to Luvie, April 6, 1937; 2.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 20, 1936; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Schenectady General Electric, January 5, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, January 9, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding 1938 Congress of Industrial Organization Convention, January 23, 1939; 6.
      - Elmoe Herrick Regarding National Labor Relations Board with NLRB Form, September 26, 1935; 7.
      - James Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, October 16, 1835; 8.
      - Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, General Electric, Company Unions and UE Unions with Petition, November 6, 1935; 9.
      - Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Schenectady General Electric, January 4, 1936; 10.
      - Winifred Moveis Regarding Mailing List, April 25, 1936; 11.
    - Local 301 Outgoing William Turnbull Correspondence, September 21, 1935-April 16, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 47)
      - William Turnbull to National Labor Relations Board Regarding Company Union, Hours, Unemployment, NLRB, Schenectady General Electric and Electrical Radio Workers Union, September 21, 1935; 1.
      - Turnbull to James Matles Regarding Company Union, Electrical Radio Workers Union and Schenectady General Electric, October 11, 1935; 2.
      - Turnbull to Matles Regarding Company Union, National Labor Relations Board, Schenectady General Electric and Electrical Radio Workers Union with October 2, 1935, Turnbull Letter to E.D. Spicer, December 11, 1935; 3.
      - Turnbull to James Carey Regarding Political Action and Farmer Labor Party, April 15, 1936; 4.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding Membership and Schenectady General Electric, April 16, 1937; 5.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding Newspaper, April 21, 1936; 6.
      - Turnbull to Carey Regarding Wages, Local 301 General Electric Collective Bargaining and Schenectady General Electric, June 16, 1936; 7.
      - Turnbull to Carey Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Schenectady General Electric and Company Union, October 24, 1936; 8.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding NLRB, Schenectady General Electric and Company Union, November 18, 1936; 9.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding General Electric Conference, January 2, 1937; 10.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding Wages, January 5, 1937; 11.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding Local 301 Officers, January 8, 1937; 12.
      - Turnbull to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 12, 1937; 13.
      - Turnbull to Carey Regarding Schenectady and Pittsfield General Electric, March 8, 1937; 14.
    - Local 301 Incoming Sol Vottis Correspondence, November 13-December 22, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - James Carey Regarding Chamber of Commerce, Schenectady General Electric and Local 602 General Electric Strikes, November 13, 1936; 1.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Membership, April 8, 1936; 2.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 301 Picnic, June 16, 1936; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes, June 16, 1936; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Women and Dues, June 29, 1936; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, Schenectady General Electric and Local 103 RCA Strikes, July 25, 1936; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Company Union, August 4, 1936; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Illion, Camden RCA and National Labor Relations Board, August 22, 1936; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Weber Electric, August 28, 1936; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 602 General Electric Strikes, September 12, 1936; 10.
      - Emspak Regarding Schenectady General Electric, National Labor Relations Board and Company Union, September 12, 1936; 11.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Supplies, September 28, 1936; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Schenectady General Electric, October 2, 1936; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, October 13-24, 1936; 14-15.
      - Emspak Regarding Labor History, October 30, 1936; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Schenectady General Electric, November 4, 1936; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding Weber Electric, Schenectady General Electric, Congress of Industrial Organization and Company Union, November 9, 1936; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages, Schenectady General Electric and Companu Union, November 14, 1936; 19.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Schenectady General Electric, December 22, 1936; 20.
    - Local 301 Incoming Sol Vottis Correspondence, July 13, 1937-February 2, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 13-November 9, 1937; 1-2.
      - Emspak Regarding Pittsfield General Electric and Finances, November 20, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and Stromberg Carlson, December 18, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Unemployment, May 3, 1938; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 601, May 4, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 20-June 6, 1938; 7-8.
      - Emspak Regarding Maytag and Philco Strikes, July 25, 1938; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, August 18-September 23, 1938; 10-11.
      - Emspak Regarding 1938 Officers Report and Women, September 23, 1938; 12.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances and UE Constitutions, October 24, 1938; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding UE Constitutions, October 26, 1938; 14.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 29, 1938-April 26, 1939; 15-16.
      - Emspak Regarding Singer Strikes, May 22, 1939; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 24, 1939; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding Teamsters with Business List, August 28, 1939; 19.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, October 28-December 28, 1939; 20-22.
      - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 2, 1940; 23.
    - Local 301 Incoming Sol Vottis Correspondence, November 19, 1937-February 3, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 23-June 20, 1940; 1-2.
      - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 13, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, October 30-November 13, 1940; 4-6.
      - Emspak Regarding Guards, November 27, 1940; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 22, 1941; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Kirkland Lake Mine, Mill and Smelter Strikes, February 9, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Finances, March 31, 1943-February 3, 1944; 10-16.